<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://MariaEriksson.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 19:43:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/publications/</guid><description>Publications Eriksson, Maria; Whitaker, Kirstie; Booth, John; et al. Pediatric epilepsy surgery from 2000 to 2018: Changes in referral and surgical volumes, patient characteristics, genetic testing, and post-surgical outcomes. Epilepsia. 2023 Jun 2. doi: 10.1111/epi.17670. Epub ahead of print. PMID: 37264783.
Eriksson, Maria; Ripart, Mathilde; Piper, Rory; et al. Predicting seizure outcome after epilepsy surgery: Do we need more complex models, larger samples, or better data? Epilepsia. 2023 May 2. doi: https://doi.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 19:43:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a PhD student based jointly at UCL Institute of Child Health and Great Ormond Street Hospital. I am supervised by Professor Torsten Baldeweg and Professor Helen Cross. My PhD is funded by NIHR Great Ormond Street Hospital Biomedical Research Centre as part of the UCL Child Health Research PhD Programme.
In October 2020, I was awarded the UCL Research Scholarship for Cross-Disciplinary Training to undertake an additional year of training at the Alan Turing Institute, the UK&amp;rsquo;s national institute for data science and machine learning.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 19:43:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://MariaEriksson.github.io/work/</guid><description>Invited Talks &amp;amp; Conferences Oral Presentation, British Paediatric Neurology Association Conference, Edinburgh, UK, January 2023
Oral Presentation, Young Epilepsy Research Retreat, Crawley, UK, January 2023
Poster Presentation, 14th European Epilepsy Congress, Geneva, Switzerland, July 2022
Oral Presentation, Young Epilepsy Research Retreat, Virtual, January 2022
Oral Presentation, UCL Cognitive Neuroscience and Neuropsychiatry Section, Virtual, December 2021
Oral Presentation, 34th International Epilepsy Congress, Virtual, August 2021
Oral Presentation, Great Ormond Street Hospital Neurosciences Group, Virtual, June 2021</description></item></channel></rss>